pressplay.io 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - PressPlay

Your privacy is of great importance to us. This Privacy Policy exists to tell you what kind of information we may gather while you visit our website and how we may use such information.

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about individuals with two exceptions: when such information is voluntarily submitted by the visitor through forms, and some incidental statistics of site usage which are collected automatically.

**Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

In order to enable visitors of our website to see certain pages, when specifically requested by them, we require some contact information, (such as name, and e-mail address). The information collected shall be used for the purposes specified when it was collected, to respond to visitor’s inquiries, and fulfill e-mail messaging programs to notify visitors about new content or services on our website.

Any information given to us shall be stored and managed the greatest care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. We will not sell, rent, or exchange such personally identifiable information to any other organization or entity. Notwithstanding the above, we may indeed disclose personal information if required to do so by subpoenas, court orders or legal process or when such disclosure is made for establishment or exercise of legal rights or in defending against legal claim, or as otherwise required by law.

If you decide you no longer wish to receive postal mailings and/or e-mails from us, please let us know by sending an e-mail or writing to us and telling us you no longer wish to receive postal mail and/or e-mail. Please provide us with your exact name, postal address, and/or e-mail address. We will make sure your name is removed from our mailing list.

**Information Automatically Collected and Stored**

In common with many websites, we also measure the performance of our website in order to improve and customize it in favor of our visitors. During your visit, we may automatically collect and temporarily store certain usage information about visits to our websites. This information may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring/ existing pages and URLs, domain names, pages viewed and the date and time of your request and other such information that uniquely identify your browser. Such information is used for system administration and for producing usage statistics. We may entrust third parties with the described performance measurement. Such third parties will be required to use appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Our website may deposit certain bits of information called “cookies” in a visitor’s computer. Generally, a cookie assigns a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Cookies can tell us how and when pages in a website are visited and by how many people. This technology does not collect an individual visitor’s identifying information; rather, this information is also in an aggregate form. The purpose of this technology and the information it provides is again to help us improve our website. Most web browsers allow the user to deny or accept the cookie feature. However, please note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with certain features (e.g. customized delivery of information) available on our website. Further information about cookies can be found at http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx

**REMARKETING AND BEHAVIORAL TARGETING**

We reserve the right to participate with third party advertising partners in remarketing and behavioral targeting programs. These services allow us and our partners to display ads that are likely to be more relevant (such as behavioral or targeted ads that are based on information about your browsing history). This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using cookies to transfer information to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.

These third party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies and other tracking devices to track your activities on this site to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies. Tracking may include, but not limited to, the following: first party cookies, third party cookies, anonymous cookies, persistent identifiers, email optin, and search engine keywords. We have no access or control over these cookies and other tracking devices that may be used by third party advertisers, and we have no responsibility or liability for the policies and practices of these sites.

AdWords Remarketing (Google) - We reserve the right to participate in AdWords Remarketing which is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity of this site with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick cookie. Information collected: cookie and Usage Data. For the opt-out, visit https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en

Remarketing through Google Analytics for Display Advertising (Google) - We reserve the right to participate in any and all of the following Google Analytics Advertising Features provided by Google Inc. -   Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. These features use first party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) for connecting the tracking activity performed by Google Analytics and its cookies with the Adwords advertising network and the DoubleClick cookie (a third party cookie). Information collected: cookie and Usage Data, including audience data such as age, gender, and interests. For the opt-out, visit https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en You may optout of the Google Analytics service with the Google's Browser Add-on that's available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/

For information in general about Google's remarketing ad campaigns, and specifically about information regarding DoubleClick cookies and how to control and manage Google's advertising cookies for these campaigns, visit http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/

For another Google resource for opting out of Google's use of cookies, visit http://www.google.com/settings/ads

For information regarding how Google uses data when you use Google's partners' sites or apps, visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/

For anther resource recommended by Google for opting out of a third party vendor's use of cookies, visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

Custom Audience (Facebook). We reserve the right to participate in Facebook.com's Custom Audience. A Custom Audience on Facebook.com enables us to display to persons on our email lists targeted, personalized ads when they visit Facebook.com. The ads are based on your shopping experience at our website. No personal information, including your shopping history, is shared with Facebook. The Custom Audience allows us to convert your email address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers that Facebook generates from email addresses of its users. You may optout of participation in our Facebook Custom Audience by sending an email, from the email address you are opting out of, to the email address provided in our contact information below. For your optout to be effective, you must: (i) place the following text in the subject line of the email - "Opting Out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads", and (ii) in the body of the email, include your name and email address. We will forward your name and email address to Facebook.com with a request to delete you from all of our Facebook Custom Audience Ads.

AdRoll Remarketing (Google) - We reserve the right to participate in AdRoll Remarketing which is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service (Interest-Based advertising) provided by AdRoll, Inc. and based on passing tracking cookies. You should note that although most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, you may be able to change your browser settings to cause your browser to refuse first party or third-party cookies or to indicate when a third-party cookie is being sent. However, disabling or limiting cookies may cause certain features of this service to not function properly or optimally. Check your browser’s “Help” files or other similar resources to learn more about handling cookies on your browser. You may opt out of Interest-Based advertising delivered using HTTP cookies by accessing this web page:

Other Remarketing Services. We reserve the right to participate in additional remarketing services that will be similar to the remarketing services described above. These services will allow us and our partners to display ads that are likely to be more relevant (such as behavioral or targeted ads that are based on information about your browsing history). If you require any information regarding these services, including without limitation, how to opt out of such services, please contact please contact our site as provided below under "Contact Us".

**Linked Sites**

Links on this Site to websites are provided as a convenience to you. Such linked sites are outside our control and responsibility and are not covered by this policy. If you use any such linked sites, you should consult the privacy policies posted on those websites.

**User’s Data**

Upon a user’s request, we shall remove all the user’s data from the website. All removed user’s data shall be kept for three additional months (offline) before deletion.

**Security**

Although we take necessary measures in order to provide a secure website we can not fully control and therefore can not be liable for all interruptions, intrusions, errors, loss of data or any other interferences with the use of this website caused by a breach of security.

**Limitation of Liability**

Under no circumstances, including but not limited to negligence, shall we be liable for any special or consequential damages that results from the use of, or the inability to use, the website and the materials in it.

Without derogating the aforementioned, in no event shall our total liability exceed the amount paid by you, if any, for accessing the site.

**Contact information**

For any question or to request modification or deletion of your personal information, please e-mail support@nutshellmetrics.com

**Changes and Updates to this Policy**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will provide notification of the change on our website. The Privacy Policy does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.
